# Bertin "Ben" Koala

ben.koala123@gmail.com

Tel:

### **SUMMARY**

Focused and quick-learning Engineer with one year of experience in web design using javascript programming, html, css and various frameworks and databases. Managed various projects to implement multiple websites working with consulting companies. Worked on projects implemented with Heroku and Mysql. I have also led multiple projects for the acquisition of tools and equipment used in RF measurement systems (script used for automation include python and Mathlab). I also led the analysis, design and implementation of software tools and systems used for data collection.

# **EDUCATION**

University Of Washington
June 21 – December 21

Certificate in Full stack Web Development

University Of Washington October 2016 – June 2018 *Master in Business Administration* 

University Of Washington October 1993 – June 1995 *Master in Electrical Engineering* 

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Independent Web Developer**

2017 - Current

- Integrate code changes, test code changes, and document code changes
- Developed PHP scripts to translate data between applications
- Developed automation scripts to test storage appliances in Python
- Practice agile development methodologies and work with current networking technologies
- Built website and make modification with php and Mysql
- Wrote php scripts to load data and parse Api responses
- Work on design and implement of various networks.

### **The Boeing Company**

2005 - Current

- Wrote, modified, and debugged internal website for custom application
- Wrote scripts to interface with measurement equipments
- Developed HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and JSP pages for user interaction
- Wrote Python scripts to load data and parse XML documents

## **SKILLS**

- Full stack Web developer certificate
- Javascript
- Linux
- Php
- MySql
- Html
- Jquery
- Css
- Handlebars framework